<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>My Site - Travel</title><link href="https://thanks4allthefish.github.io/site/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://thanks4allthefish.github.io/site/feeds/travel.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://thanks4allthefish.github.io/site/</id><updated>2021-06-20T10:20:00+05:30</updated><entry><title>The Land They Call Paradise</title><link href="https://thanks4allthefish.github.io/site/the-land-they-call-paradise.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-06-20T10:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-06-20T10:20:00+05:30</updated><author><name>thanks4fish</name></author><id>tag:thanks4allthefish.github.io,2021-06-20:/site/the-land-they-call-paradise.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;… … see this! Dude, wake up! You have to see this!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I found Akshay grinning at my bleary eyed confusion and tried to figure out where I was. There was another sleeping shape beside me and outside the window, the grass on hill slope was wet with the morning dew. With …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;… … see this! Dude, wake up! You have to see this!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I found Akshay grinning at my bleary eyed confusion and tried to figure out where I was. There was another sleeping shape beside me and outside the window, the grass on hill slope was wet with the morning dew. With my sense of place restored, I followed my friend to the balcony, gingerly plodding on the cold marble floor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was our first morning in Pelling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Kanchenjunga" src="./images/Kanchenjunga.jpeg" width="480"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had arrived the previous night, after a tiring seven hour trip from Gangtok. Our cab from Gyazing dropped us off at a deserted intersection of 3 variously sloping roads. Hotels lined the entire street. It was off-season and not many tourists were around. We looked at several rooms to find one that fit our miserly student budgets and possibly afforded a view of the Kanchenjunga. After looking at rooms in 3 hotels with the view blocked by the same tree, we walked downhill a bit to get away from the inconsiderate tree. Turning a corner, we found ourselves on another sloping road. We decided to try our luck at the first hotel. The reception was manned by a massive golden retriever who was intently watching the television. After looking for help that was not forthcoming from this canine receptionist, we found a human to talk to us.  After a bit of haggling, we got a cozy room with a view towards the mountain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It depends on the weather. Lately, it’s been a bit foggy”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We sat in the chilly balcony and watched the dark hillside sprinkled with lights mirroring the starry sky above. The cold darkness put us in the mood of tales about mountains and wild animals. We talked about The Man Eater of Rudraprayag, Jim Corbett, Rusty and Ruskin Bond, as Lagaan was playing on the TV.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Travel"></category></entry></feed>